

IVAN MARTIĆ

SOFTWARE & WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- ivan.martic.ri@gmail.com
- +385 91 200 8778
- Široli 14c 51216 Viškovo Croatia
- s imartic14
- https://imartic.github.io

TECHNOLOGIES

C# MS SQL SERVER

HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY VUE.JS GIT

TFS

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH | GERMAN

CROATIAN

ABOUT MF

I am a Software and Web Developer and fresh graduate of Telematics with passion for programming and design. I have over 1 year professional experience as a Software Developer developing mainly for desktop, but have also worked on several web-based projects. Lately I am focusing on Front-end web development and learning about the latest frameworks like Vue and React. When I am not programming, I try to do some design work and sports.

EXPERIENCE

ALARM AUTOMATIKA

NOV 2016 - PRESENT

Working as Software Developer in Research & Development department at Alarm automatika d.o.o. Worked on several different projects and the ones I worked most on are a self-ticketing cashier for parking lots and a web application for event management (ticketing system) and supervision.

For development I mainly used C#, JavaScript/jQuery, HTML, CSS and Microsoft SQL

Server.

IMPULS ING

NOV 2015 - JUL 2016

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Worked as Software Developer at Impulsing d.o.o. Responsible for the development of a module for an existing desktop application. Worked with C# and Microsoft SQL Server (Transact-SQL).

EDUCATION

POLYTECHNIC OF RIJEKA

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING, TELEMATICS

OCT 2012 - MAR 2017

Bachelor's degree in Telematics. Software Development/Engineering (C++, Java, SQL), Automation, Telecommunications, Electrical engineering, System design,...

TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES WILDAU

NOV 2015 - JUL 2016

TELEMATICS

Exchange semester at TH Wildau. Software project (JavaFX) and German language.